“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
ELlJAH: Previously on The Originals ;
杀了他
如果我们不能
Kill him. If we can't all create
联手合作，那还有什么意义？
some sort of community,
then what's the point?
不如杀掉彼此早点了事
Kill each other
and get it all over with.
如果你我都不能和平相处
ELIJAH; If there is no peace between us,
那你怎么能指望其他人跟随呢？
then how can you expect
others to follow suit?
这个城市的居民不会遵守这个协定的
KLAUS: The city's inhabitants will
not adhere to this agreement.
马赛尔杰拉德要我们带个消息
We have a message from Marcel Gerard.
（永无宁日）
我们两个订婚了
You and I were betrothed.
我想这就让我们变得跟皇室一样了
I guess that makes us
kind of like royalty.
我们缔结了一个联盟
这对狼人将是个重大转折
We made an alliance that's gonna
change everything for the wolves.
- 与谁结盟？
- 克劳斯
-An alliance with who?
-Klaus.
月光戒指保护狼人免受诅咒之苦
A moonlight ring to protect
werewolves from the curse.
你想要我怎么做？
What do I have to do?
我被下咒了
我不知道我还剩多长时间
I've been hexed, and
I don't know how long I have.
药物不管用了
The pills, they're not working.
这种诅咒是由魔法开始的
These hexes, they start with magic.
它们会改变大脑的化学物质
They alter the very
chemistry of the brain.
我没法恢复了
I can't be fixed?
只有死亡，我的，还有你的
There's only death.
Mine and yours.
这是主的身体，这是主的血
This is the body.
This is the blood.
愿能洗清我的罪过，保护我的灵魂
直到永远
May they cleanse me of sin and
preserve my soul in life everlasting.
现在是不是有点晚了，神父
I'd say it's a little late
for that, Father.
看来你仍坚持着你的信仰
I see you still have your faith.
- 别过来
- 可惜它终究无法拯放你
-Stay back.
-lf only it could save you.
西恩，天啊，不
Sean, God, no!
敬永生
To life everlasting.
- 喝吧
滚开，魔鬼
-Drink.
-Be gone, demon!
来吧，就一口
Come now, just one sip.
不
No.
我知道你是谁，你这可恶的贱人
I know who you are,
you hateful bitch.
西恩，我试着…
Oh, Sean, I tried....
我试着帮助你，试着拯救你
I tried to help you.
I tried to save you.
但这个城市…
But this city....
这个城市有着太多恶魔
This city is full of monsters.
是啊，相信我，我很清楚
Yeah. Trust me, I know.
记得提醒我永远别招惹女巫
Remind me to never piss off a witch.
帮我扶着他侧躺
Help me get him on his side.
卡蜜
Cami.
基兰叔叔？
Uncle Kieran?
你要对我做什么？
What do you want from me?
你也看到了，对吧？
You saw that, right?
虽然只有一瞬间
但那就是他
It was just for a second,
but it was him.
我不知道，卡蜜
I don't know, Cami.
也许在这疯狂之下他的本性还在
I mean, maybe he's still in
there underneath all the crazy,
但这疯狂太严重了
but the crazy is pretty thick.
或许他的大脑需要刺激一下
Maybe he just needs
a shock to his system,
把不好的东西清除
something to wipe the slate clean.
小约，我想我有办法能治好他
Josh, I think I have an idea
on how to fix him.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：无畏死亡
主演：约瑟夫摩根
(BOOKS CLATTERlNG)
在找什么？需要帮忙吗？
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Can I help you find something?
是的，我想你能帮上忙
Yes. In fact, I believe you can.
我在找一本书，大概这么大
I'm looking for a book,
about yea big,
上面记录着母亲的那些强大咒语
主演：菲比托金
filled with our mother's
most powerful spells.
看样子不知所踪了
It appears to have been misplaced.
真悬啊
-How very mysterious.
-lndeed.
确实，起初我担心
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
At first, I feared
the witches had succeeded
是不是被那些女巫拿去了
in their efforts to obtain it,
但考虑到她们上次尝试的结果是
主演：莉雅派普斯
but considering
their last attempt ended
我把那位大块头纹身男的双手砍下来
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
with me relieving a rather
large, tattooed gentleman
我开始怀疑
of his hands, I began to wonder
会不会是家贼难防
if the thief wasn't
a bit closer to home.
别让我难做事，哥哥
Don't make this harder
than it needs to be, brother.
说实话，我确实怀疑你突然对
Well, admittedly, I did have a
theory that your sudden interest
母亲的魔法书感兴趣，是不是因为你
in mother's grimoire was in some way
related to whatever foolishness
和新月族狼人之间那愚蠢的勾当
you've been conducting
with the Crescent wolves.
因此，我自作主张
Therefore, I took it
upon myself to carefully
将魔法书安放到了别处，以防有人垂涎
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
place it where naughty,
little fingers could not pry.
我还以为所有人之中你最清楚
制片：兰斯安德森
And here I thought you,
of all people,
我只是想帮助那些狼人
would understand, I am simply
trying to help those wolves.
你可以说我是慈悲为怀
Play Samaritan to the abused,
或者是保护弱小也行
champion to the underdog,
so to speak.
那你还真是高尚
制片：邦妮怀斯
How splendidly noble of you.
难道你没想过
制片：邦妮怀斯
Have you ever considered
that, like you,
和你一样
我只是想保护海莉的安全
I am trying to keep Hayley safe,
用我们母亲的魔法让他们变得更强大
using our mother's magic
to empower her people
这样才有能力保护她？
so they are capable
of protecting her?
话是这么说
除非他们决定以此来报复
Yes, unless, of course,
they decide to seek retribution
多年被流放之仇
for decades held in exile.
这样海莉将会被卷入一场叛乱中
编剧：艾胥莉莱尔，巴特尼克森
And Hayley will find herself
in the middle of an uprising.
那只会引发更多的暴力冲突
导演：凯莉赛勒斯
One that will only
provoke further violence.
你这么做很有可能挑起
纽奥良的战火，弟弟
You see, you risk turning New
Orleans into a war zone, brother.
我绝不允许此事发生
I won't let that happen.
战争在我们回来之前早已揭开序慕
The drums of war were beating
long before we returned.
我建议你还是少说话，多倾听
I suggest you use a little less of
this and a little more of these.
绝对不行
Whoa, no way.
卡蜜，小约已经告诉我事情有多严重了
Cami, Josh told
me how bad things have gotten.
我应该陪在你身边，让我帮你
I should be there for you.
Just let me help.
怎么帮？让自己去送死吗？
How, by getting yourself killed?
如今你正被人追杀，马赛尔
You have a target
on your back, Marcel.
我最不愿看到的就是你因为我而受伤
The last thing I need is for
you to get hurt because of me.
我更担心你，基兰很危险
I'm more worried about you.
Kieran's dangerous.
我能应付得来
I got this.
你要是过来，我就亲自
把你赶出去，知道吗？
You come here, I'll throw
you out myself, all right?
我说真的
I mean it.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell?
好吧，没错
OK. Yeah.
这里的气氛确实有点像犯罪现场
Totally see how we got kind of a
crime scene vibe happening here.
不用害怕，好吗？
Just don't freak out, OK?
你好，我是薛斯基医生
Hi. I'm Dr. Sheski.
我只是要检查一下你的脉搏
-Just gonna get your pulse.
-(SHOUTS, SNARLS)
开口之前要仔细想清楚
Think very carefully
before you speak.
你的声音很可能让我后悔
The sound of your voice
is likely to make me
我对你所展现出的仁慈
regret what mercy
I've shown thus far.
是的，我知道
我在你的黑名单上
Yeah, yeah. I know, I'm on your
"who's been naughty" list.
问题是，卡蜜需要你
Thing is, Cami needs you.
你对我的愤怒
不要牵连到她身上
Whatever anger you have towards
me, don't make her suffer for it.
她和基兰在一起
She's with Kieran.
我必须让当局知道
I'm gonna have to let
the authorities know
这里发生了什么事
what the hell is going on here.
- 小约
- 对了
-Josh?
-Oh, right.
老兄，别慌
Dude, be cool.
只是个神父由于吸血鬼的原因
被女巫下咒了
It's just a priest hexed by a
witch because of some vampires.
接受这些现实，然后忘记它们
Accept that these things
are real, then forget them.
我是说等一下，等一下再忘记
I mean later.
You forget them later.
该死，好吧，我重新说
Crap. OK. Let me start over.
薛斯基医生
我叔叔需要镇定剂，强效的
Dr. Sheski, my uncle needs
to be sedated, something strong.
镇定剂？
他看起来需要进加护病房
Sedation?
He looks like he should be in an lCU.
是啊，另一个女巫对他施了边界咒
Yeah. See, this other witch
put this boundary spell on him.
所以他被困在这里了
So he's kind of stuck in here.
这个人营养不良
严重脱水
This man is malnourished,
severely dehydrated.
所以才请你来
但首先，医生
Which is why you're here.
But first, doctor,
你了解休克疗法吗？
what do you know
about shock therapy?
电痉挛疗法？
ECT?
首先，那十分危险
First, it's incredibly dangerous.
但众所周知，它被用来治疗极端精神病
But it has been known to help
treat cases of extreme psychosis?
回答这位女士的问题
Answer the nice lady.
我们还不完全了解这种疗法
但是的，有些病人
We don't fully understand it yet,
but, yes, in some patients,
利用电流诱发痉孪
using electrical current
to induce seizures
可以阻止精神病的发作
事实上就是重启大脑
can subvert a psychotic episode,
in effect, rebooting the brain,
但只在非常极端的情况下
我们才会考虑…
but only in the most extreme
cases, do we even consider--
就像我朋友讲的
我们说的是一个神父被女巫下了咒
Like my friend said, we're talking
about a priest hexed by a witch.
我想不出比这更极端的情况了
I don't think it gets
any more extreme than that.
就这样
That's it.
吸气
吐气
Inhale and release.
这就意味着不打无痛分娩针了吧？
I guess this means no epidural, huh?
你确定我不能在医院那种
You sure I can't do this
thing in, say, a hospital,
有医生有药物的环境下生产吗？
you know, the place
with the doctors and the drugs?
亲爱的，狼人在你出生之前
Honey, the werewolves have been
having babies out here
就一直在这里生产
别担心了
since before you were born.
Stop worrying.
好吧
然后呢，伊芙？
OK.
Then what, Eve?
我都不知道有妈妈是什么感觉
更别说当妈妈了
I don't even know what it's like to
have a mother, let alone be one.
相信我，到了那个时候
你自然就会知道怎么做
Trust me, when the time comes,
you'll know exactly what to do.
希望如此
I hope so.
虽然想像克劳斯换尿布很有趣
As fun as it is to image Klaus
changing dirty diapers,
但我确定我要一个人做这些了
I'm pretty sure
that I'll be doing this alone.
我倒不这么认为
I somehow doubt that.
抱歉打扰了
Pardon the interruption.
我希望能跟疑似叛乱同谋
I wonder if I might have a quick word
简单说几句话
with the conspirators
of a supposed uprising.
你们正在犯一个很大的错误
You're making a grave mistake.
所以你在担心我们，是吗？
So you're just worried about us.
Is that it?
听着，以利亚
我们知道你弟弟的名声不好
Look, Elijah, we know all about
your brother's reputation,
但即使只有很小的机会
这些戒指可以帮我们
but if there is even a chance
that these rings can help us
控制住诅咒…
take control of our curse--
或者说天赋
Our gift.
那么坦白说
我们不在乎他真正的目的
Then, honestly, we don't
care what he's really after.
- 也没必要在乎
- 我懂了
-Won't have to.
-I see.
但法语区里有些人
There are those in the Quarter
会认为这是很严重的挑衅
who will consider this
a great provocation.
很显然，很多人认为我们呼吸都是挑衅
Apparently, most of them see
us breathing the same way.
你看着我的眼睛签着了宣誓词
You signed a pledge, and you looked
me in the eye as you did so.
我们也不想要战争，以利亚
We don't want a fight, Elijah.
我们只是想要更好的生活
We just want a better life.
和我弟弟结盟绝不可能达到这个目的
Allegiance with my brother will
guarantee you anything but that.
怎么回事？
What the hell?
你们谁说了算？
Which one of you is in charge?
你是谁？
Who's asking?
海莉，你还好吗？
(MUFFLED) Hayley, are you OK?
没事的，来，过来
It's OK. Here. Come here.
天啊
Oh, God.
杰克森
Jackson?
来，把他带走
Here. Get him away from here.
来吧
Come on.
- 海莉
- 以利亚
-Hayley.
-Elijah.
附子草
Wolfsbane.
一定是放在油箱里了
It must have been in the gas tank.
你速度最快
You're the fastest.
带着他，还有那些不能自己走的
Take him, anyone else who
can't walk on their own.
没事，以利亚，我很好
It's OK, Elijah. I'm fine.
他们需要你的帮助
They need your help.
撑着点，好吗？
Just hang in there, OK?
奥利佛，不要
Oliver, no.
- 啊！
- 按住这里
-Oh, God.
-Press here.
把你的衬衫给我，快
Give me your shirt. Now!
没事的
It's OK.
你怎么学会这些的？
How'd you learn how to do that?
如果你13岁就离家
你会学到很多东西
You get a hell of an education
when you leave home at 13.
这样能减缓失血
至少在伤口愈合之前
That should slow the bleeding,
at least until the healing kicks in.
吸血鬼
The vampires.
他们甚至没胆自己动手
干这种龌龊事
They don't even have the guts to
do their own dirty work themselves.
干嘛自己动手
反正可以魅惑
I mean, why bother
when you can just compel
无辜的人来做事
some poor son of a bitch
to do it for you?
我们要狠狠地反击
I say we hit them back, hard.
在这待着，奥利佛
Stay here, Oliver.
我需要你在我回来之前照顾大家
I need you to look after
everyone until I get back.
- 你要去哪？
- 如果这是吸血鬼干的
-Where the hell are you going?
-lf this was vampires,
那我很确定是谁下的命令
I'm pretty sure that I can guess
who gave the order.
我要去找马赛尔
I'm gonna go find Marcel.
地狱里有个专门给
你们这类怪物待的地方
There's a special place
in hell for your kind.
我可不是第一次听到这种话
Not the first time
I've heard that one.
瞧瞧这个阴森的小地方
Well, isn't this
a gruesome, little scene?
克劳斯，你来干什么？
Klaus, what are you doing here?
我接到一通以你为名义的紧急电话
I received an urgent call
on your behalf.
然后我好像接到了个任务
It seems I've been tasked with doing
要做件你的胆小鬼男友做不到的事
what your coward
of a boyfriend could not,
看这情况应该是要劝阻你
which, by the looks of things,
is dissuading you
别干现在这件蠢事
from whatever madness
it is you're about to attempt.
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
拜托，我求求你了
别逼我干这事
Please, I'm begging you,
don't force me to do this.
好啊，那我自己来
Fine. I'll do it myself.
卡蜜儿，你叔叔是个好人
-(MACHlNE POWERS UP)
-Camille, your uncle is a good man.
他不该受这种苦
He shouldn't suffer.
他已经受了好几个星期的苦了
他快死了，克劳斯
He's been suffering for weeks.
He's dying, Klaus.
这说不定是他能活下来的唯一机会
This might be the only
chance he's got.
海莉
Hayley.
我得去处理一些事
我会尽快回来
I have to take care of something.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
- 你在哪？
- 以利亚，我没事
-Where are you?
-Elijah, I'm fine.
我不在的时候帮我照顾狼群，好吗？
Just take care of the pack
while I'm gone, please?
她没事吧？
Is she OK?
看样子是的
Apparently, yes.
还好炸弹在那里爆炸了
It's a good thing that bomb
went off where it did.
不然情况可能更糟
Could've been a lot worse.
可能会有人死掉
People could've got killed.
除非
Unless....
带所有人离开这
Get everyone out of here....
快
Now!
（教堂 肃静区）
卡蜜
Cami....
你到底对我做了什么？
What the hell did you do to me?
- 我们得再来一次
- 你认真的吗？
-We have to do it again.
-Are you serious?
这是有关系 的，它已经起作用了
That was something coherent.
It's working.
医生，照顾好你的病人
Doctor, see to your patient.
离我远点
You get away from me.
心跳不正常
Heartbeat's irregular.
不能继续电击了，他会死的
You can't keep this up.
It'll kill him.
不
- 卡蜜
-No.
-Cami.
我们得好好谈谈
私底下谈
We need to have a word in private.
我想你要做好心理准备
I think you need to prepare yourself.
这事可能不会圆满结束
This story does not
have a happy ending.
- 但这个治疗方法…
- 会害死他的
-But the treatments--
-Will kill him.
如果是你亲手加速你叔叔的死亡
Were you to push him over the brink,
我不愿看到你一生背负这样的愧疚
I would hate for you
to have to live with that,
不管你的初衷有多么高尚
no matter how noble your aim.
所以就这样了吗？
你要我就这样放弃吗？
So that's it, then?
You just expect me to surrender?
也许是时候了
Maybe it's time.
不是放弃
而是放手
Not to give up, to let go.
这不是你说了算
It's not your decision to make.
杰克森，她已经死了
Jackson, she's gone.
救命！快来人！
OLlVER: Help! Somebody help!
好，撑住，撑住，伊芙
-(EVE GROANlNG)
-OK. Hold on. Hold on, Eve.
撑住，伊芙
撑住
Come on, Eve.
Come on.
没事的
It's OK.
你一个大肚姿敢来这，胆子不小啊
You got some nerve
coming up in here, mama.
有人今早在河口攻击了我的狼群
Someone attacked my pack
in the bayou this morning,
而我在这也没见着什么聪明人
and since I don't see any genius
mastermind types around here...
你不如乖乖告诉我马赛尔在哪
...why don't you just tell me
where Marcel is
然后我们就可以继续各自过生活
and we can both get
on with our day.
你以为我在开玩笑吗？
You think I'm playing?
受伤的都是我的家人
There were families out there.
他以前经常去一个地方
派特森路1917号
He used to keep a place....
1917 Patterson.
如果他还没走的话，他应该在那个地方
If he's still around, he'll be there.
如果我是你，我不会离他那么近
I wouldn't stay that close
to him if I were you.
他现在有点难以捉摸，还有点嗜杀
He's kind of unpredictable
and murdery.
太奇妙了
This is fascinating.
去找对他下咒的女巫谈谈会有用吗？
Would it be possible to speak
to the witches responsible?
是啊，我劝你别干傻事
Yeah. You don't want to do that.
我的天…
Holy--
来个人帮一下忙
Hey! Little help in here!
克劳斯，你在哪？
Klaus, where are you?
恶魔，主的愤怒之火向你燃烧
- 这不可能
-His wrath burns against you, demon.
-This is not happening.
我这里有点小状况，亲爱的
I'm in a bit of
a situation here, love.
有人今早在河口丢了枚人肉炸弹
Somebody sent a suicide bomber
out to the bayou this morning.
什么？你现在在哪？
What? Where are you?
- 我在城里，我没事
- 给我
-I'm in the city now. I'm fine.
-Give it to me.
我想这种攻击一定是马赛尔干的
I figured an attack like
that must have been Marcel.
他这么多年来一直恨狼人
He's hated the wolves for years,
还跟女巫搞了这么多事出来
and after that stunt he pulled
with the witches....
所以我现在在找他
So I tracked him down.
他这么费力想把我们炸死
I thought you might like
to help kick his ass
你应该会想一起去教训他吧
for trying to blow us
to kingdom come.
你现在把他弄出去吧
Would you get him
out of here now, please?
要确保他什么都记不得
好，海莉，听着
Make sure he remembers nothing.
All right, Hayley, listen,
我跟你保证，等我把这边的事搞定
I assure you,
once I am finished here,
我将会全心全意来帮你
you will have my undivided attention.
但这段时间，你别惹上麻烦
In the meantime,
please stay out of trouble.
你不用担心
You don't have to worry.
以利亚和我在一起
Elijah's with me.
伤口现在应该愈合了
That wound should be healing by now.
她从没杀过人
从没启动过狼人基因
She never killed anyone,
never activated the werewolf gene.
所以她无法自我治愈，和我们不一样
So she can't heal, not like us.
我的血能治愈她
My blood, it could heal her.
吸血鬼的血？
Vampire blood?
相信我，她宁愿死
Trust me, she'd rather die.
我们不能让他们就此逃过此事
We can't just let them
get away with this.
我们根本不知道是谁干的
We don't even know who's to blame.
不知道才怪
The hell we don't!
如果我们不反击，他们还会这么做
And if we don't fight back,
they'll just do it again.
进来
Come on in.
请坐
Have a seat.
我想给你倒杯酒，但是…
I'd offer you a drink, but....
- 地方不错
- 只是暂时的
-Sweet pad.
-It's just temporary.
朋友帮我找的
Friend hooked me up.
不管你信不信，我还是
有些分散在各处的朋友
Believe it or not, I still got
a few of those kicking around.
我需要朋友向我通风报信
I need friends to keep me informed,
提醒我有人要来
to warn me when someone's coming,
要我为没做过的事负责
Iooking to blame me
for things that I didn't do.
郑重申明
你没必要那样折磨迪亚哥
For the record, you didn't
have to work Diego like that.
我们早就该好好聊聊了
You and I are long overdue
for a chat.
你想聊？那就聊吧
You want to talk? Talk.
好凶啊
Tough girl.
这点和你爸可真像
You're a lot like
your dad in that way.
是的，我认识他
Oh, yeah. I knew him.
我认识你所有家人
I knew your whole family.
事实上，如果你像我一样了解他们
In fact, if you knew them like I did,
你就知道他们到底有多少敌人了
you'd know just how many
enemies they have.
90年代时，新月狼族
统治着这个城市
Back in the '90s, it was the Crescent
wolves who took over the city.
或者说试图统治
Or tried to.
他们天生擅长如此，做得也很好
They lived to throw down,
and they were good at it, too.
只要能掌握更多的权力
他们不在乎杀死谁
They didn't care who they killed
as long as they got more power.
所以新月族的诅咒
是你阻止他们的办法？
So the Crescent curse was
your way of stopping them?
多英勇啊
How heroic.
要么那样，要么就得杀了他们
It was either that or kill them all,
我并不热衷于残忍的大屠杀
and I'm not big
on indiscriminant slaughter.
我对孩子还是很有心的
See, I have this thing about kids.
我听说了
So I've heard.
你可不只是听说
安德莉亚拉柏奈
You did more than hear about it....
Andrea Labonair.
你就是活生生的证据
You're living proof.
他心跳停止了
你最好不要看
He's in cardiac arrest.
You might want to look away.
- 你在干什么？
- 给他的心脏做个按摩
-What the hell are you doing?
-Massaging his heart.
他的身体正在停止运转
His body is shutting down.
即使有我的帮助，他也没多少时间了
Even with my help,
he doesn't have much time.
你的血
Your blood.
如果你喂他喝你的血
他就会醒过来，对吧？
If you fed him your blood,
he'd wake back up, right?
是的，变成一个转变中的吸血鬼
As a vampire in transition, yes.
至于诅咒…
As for the hex...
也许死亡才是对他的仁慈
...perhaps his death will be a mercy.
喂他，快点
Do it. Just do it.
拜托，克劳斯
我不能让他这样死去
Please, Klaus, I can't let
him die, not like this.
你知道我的真实身份多久了？
How long have you known who I am?
我注意到你对新月狼族很感兴趣
I saw how interested you
were in those Crescents.
你们在种植园外家庭团聚之后
After your little family reunion
out at the old plantation house,
我就开始思考你们之间的联系
I started to put
two and two together.
告诉我，马赛尔
Tell me something, Marcel.
是你杀了我父母吗？
Did you kill my parents?
狼人之间发生了冲突
There was infighting
among the wolves.
你的家人很低调
有人攻击了他们
Your folks were laying low.
Somebody turned on them.
说实话，我不知道是谁
I honestly don't know who.
我之后到了那里
在你的婴儿床里发现了你
I got there afterwards,
found you in your crib.
给我一个合理的理由，我凭什么
Give me one good reason
why I should believe
要相信你说的话
anything that you have to say.
信不信由你
但你是拉怕奈家族最后一个人
Believe whatever you want,
but you were the last Labonair.
这本来可以成为我们的筹码
I mean, could've been a lot
of leverage for our side,
但我却把你交给了基兰神父
but instead,
I took you to Father Kieran.
那是什么？
What's that?
主要是钱
Money mostly.
你去安全地方重新开始所需要的东西
Stuff you need to start over
someplace safe.
不管在河口发生了什么事
都不是我干的
Whatever happened in the
bayou, I'm not your guy,
但照事情的发展来看
最终我也许不得不这么做
but the way things are going,
eventually, I might have to be.
这就是你的大计划
So this is your grand plan.
把我赶出城
克劳斯和以利亚就会紧随在后？
Get me out of town, and Klaus
and Elijah follow closely behind?
我不能说这不会是一个积极的影响
I can't say that wouldn't
be a positive side effect.
照你的建议，你为什么不自己离开？
So why don't you leave,
follow your own advice?
我在这里出生，海莉
I was born here, Hayley.
我也是
So was l.
那个骑车放炸弹的人
Guy on the bike, the bomber....
听说他有赌瘾
Word is, he had a gambling problem.
欠赌场钱
Owed money to the casinos.
更重要的是，欠那些
经营赌场的人类的钱
More importantly,
to the humans who run them.
还有，海莉，当情况变糟时
And, Hayley, when things get bad,
记住，我努力让你远离这一切了
remember, I tried to get
you clear of it.
再一次
Again.
我想我该走了
I'm afraid I have to go.
他醒来后会怎样？
What happens next, after he wakes?
会进入转变过程，嗜血
He'll be in transition,
craving blood,
但我在那之前就会回来
but I'll be back before then.
他一定会很生我的气
He's gonna be furious with me.
他是神父，我却把他变成了吸血鬼
He's a priest.
I turned him into a vampire.
那是怎样绝望的举动？
What kind of desperate move is that?
你和我都清楚，亲爱的
他一定不会完成转变
Well, you know as well as I do, love,
he'll never go through with it.
转变他并不是目的
Turning him wasn't the goal.
是给你机会跟他道别
It was to give you a
chance to say good-bye.
克劳斯，你能再多留一会吗？
Klaus, will you stay
just a little longer?
当然可以
Of course.
这就是你承诺的和平吗？
Is this the peace you promised?
我想我弟弟认为他可以解除你们的诅咒
I gather my brother believes
he can remove your curse.
克劳斯说要给我们自由
Klaus was offering us freedom,
不仅是从变身的痛苦中解脱
not just from the pain
that comes with turning,
还有我们一直以来所遭受的轻视
but from the contempt we've
faced our whole lives.
那海莉怎么办？
And what about Hayley?
想让这里变得适合她
Want to make this place
right for her,
对她和孩子都安全
safe for her and the baby.
卡蜜，发生了什么事？
Cami, what happened?
那个诅咒…
The hex....
我能感觉到
它活生生的在我身体里
I could feel it like a....
Iiving thing inside of me.
它消失了
It's gone.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
是的，今天对你来说很不客易，神父
Yes, you've had a trying day, father.
要怎么跟你说呢？
How best to break it to you?
看来诅咒随着你的死
It appears the hex was broken...
而解除了
...by your death.
等一下
Back up.
我死了吗？
I died?
死了多久？
For how long?
大约几个小时
A few hours, give or take.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能就这样失去你
I just couldn't lose you,
not like that.
我强迫克劳斯喂他的血给你
I made him give you his blood.
我明白了
I see.
我终究还是和魔鬼做了交易
So the devil has a deal
for me, after all.
基兰叔叔，我…
-(SCOFFS)
-Uncle Kieran l....
你的饥饿感
只会越来越强
That hunger you feel,
it'll only grow stronger.
我知道这会怎样
I know how it works.
那你很快就知道，如果你不喝血就会死
Then you will soon know if you
do not feed, you will die.
我知道如果这是我必须做出的选择
I know if that's the choice that l
have to make,
那我已经死了
I'm dead already.
请让我跟我侄女单独待一会
Please leave me with my niece.
我想和她单独聊聊
I'd like a private moment
to talk with her.
没事的
It's OK.
克劳斯，谢谢你今天所做的一切
Klaus, thank you for today.
谢谢你的善良
For being kind.
嘿，奥利
我看起来怎样？
Hey, Ollie. How do I look?
很好，伊芙，你看起来很好
You look fine, Evie.
You look just fine.
你总是不擅长说谎
You always were a terrible liar.
该死
Damn it.
听着，你只要触发诅咒
Look, all you got to do is
just trigger the curse.
你就会治愈
You'll heal.
这就是我们的天性，你的天性
It's who we are.
It's who you are.
你为什么就不能接受呢？
Why can't you just accept that?
为什么就没人知道该做什么呢？
Why can't anyone see
what needs to be done?
像动物一样住在这里
部落间相互斗争
Living here like animals,
fighting between tribes,
不敢为自己出头
scared to stand up for ourselves.
谁要来领导我们？
杰克森吗？
Who's gonna lead us? Jackson?
他想要屈服于那个混合种
He wants to bow down to that hybrid.
海莉吗？她不是我们的一员
Hayley? She's not one of us.
至少现在，我们有一个仇人了
At least now, we have
an enemy to hate.
奥利佛，不
Oliver, no.
- 告诉我你没有…
- 你不理解
-Tell me you didn't--
-You don't understand.
那就解释给我听，奥利
Then explain it to me, Ollie.
我了解你
I know you.
我知道你不会伤害自己人
I know you wouldn't
hurt your own people.
听着
事情不应该是这样的，伊芙
Look, it wasn't supposed to
happen like this, Evie.
我…
I just...
我只想制造点事端
让我们的人愤怒起来
I just wanted to make a little noise,
just get our people mad.
但我没同意这些
But I didn't agree to all this.
他们在背后搞鬼，现在…
They stabbed me in the back,
and now you're--
谁？是谁唆使你的？
Who? Who put you up to this?
你这个蠢孩子
You stupid kid.
你知道狼群发现后
Do you have any idea
会怎么处置你吗？
what the pack's gonna
do to you when they find out?
他们不会发现的，伊芙
They're not gonna find out, Evie.
如果发现了
If they did...
那些人就白死了
...all those people
would have died in vain.
我不得不，不惜一切代价
I had to do whatever it took...
让我们强大起来
...to make us strong.
- 奥利，不要
- 即使现在我也不得不这么做
-Ollie, no.
-And I've got to do that even now.
奥利
奥利佛，不要
Ollie. Oliver, no.
不，不，奥利
No! No! Ollie!
对不起，伊芙
I'm sorry, Eve.
所有东西都在你说的地方
Everything is where
you said it would be
除了你提到的钥匙
只有那个我没找到
except that key you mentioned.
That's the one thing I couldn't find.
是不是你经常挂在脖子上的那把？
It's the one you usually
wear around your neck?
钥匙是我们家族传承的重要一部分
That key is a very important
part of our family legacy.
你必须找到它
You have to find it.
我会的，我保证
I will, I promise.
真对不起
I am so sorry.
我从没想过要把你牵扯进来
牵扯进这一切
I never wanted to involve
you in this, in any of it.
一定不会就这样结束
This can't be how it ends.
这是唯一结束的办法
It was the only way
it was ever going to end.
我很久之前就接受了
I made peace with that
a long time ago.
听着
Listen.
我不知道情况会变得多糟
I don't know how bad
this is gonna get,
我不想让你看到
and I don't want you to see it.
所以一会儿，我会放手
So in a moment, I'm gonna let go,
你就转身
and you are gonna turn around,
离开这里，不要回头
and you are gonna walk out of
here without looking back.
好吗，孩子？
OK, kiddo?
答应我
Promise me.
不要回头
Without looking back.
他们希望我们心存怀疑
OLlVER: They are counting
on our doubts.
- 没错  - 对
-That's right!
-Yeah!
他们希望我们心存恐惧
They are counting on our fears!
- 没错  - 对
-That's right!
-Right!
你没走
You stayed.
明天一早，他们就知道
我们不是懦夫
Come morning, they will
know that we are not cowards.
怎么回事？他在干什么？
What's going on?
What is he doing?
我们无所畏惧
We are not afraid!
他在利用悲剧的发生获得权力
He's making a move for power
in the wake of tragedy.
他不是一个人
He's not alone.
你走之后又有一次攻击
There was another attack
after you left.
什么？
What?
你的朋友杰克森需要你的帮助
ELlJAH: Your friend Jackson
will need your help.
他们会想要复仇
They will want vengeance.
血债血偿
Blood for blood.
不幸的是，在困境中
And, unfortunately,
in troubled times,
人们不会听从最优秀的人
people do not look for the best.
而会选择喊得最响的人
But rather, the loudest.
没错
Yeah!
我很惊讶会在这里看到你
I'm surprised to see you here.
河口的爆炸
对我孩子的攻击
The bayou explosion,
the attack on my child.
告诉我你所知道的
Tell me what you know.
我知道狼人不缺敌人
I know the wolves have
no shortage of enemies.
- 马赛尔就是其中之一
- 马赛尔不会堕落到如此地步
-Marcel, for one.
-Marcel wouldn't stoop so low.
然而女巫…
The witches, however....
我已亲眼见识到你们的残忍
I have witnessed firsthand
the depths of your cruelty.
你不会以为是我干的吧
You don't think I did this.
你把我当成什么样的怪物了？
What kind of monster
do you take me for?
和你那纯洁无辜的宝贝卡蜜儿相比
How ugly I must seem
next to the pure,
我一定非常丑陋不堪
innocent glow of
your precious Camille.
对了，真为她叔叔难过
So sad about her uncle, by the way.
基兰正在转变过程中
Kieran is in transition.
他已经从诅咒中解脱
He has been released from the hex.
那么强大的诅咒吗？
GENEVlEVE: A hex
of that magnitude?
基兰的诅咒还会再出现
Kieran's hex will return...
迟早的事
...if it hasn't already.
神父
-No!
-Not yet, priest.
还有任务要做
There's more work to be done.
完成你苦行的最后一件事
A final offering
to complete your penance,
献上你最亲爱的人
that which you hold most dear.
另一方面，那个边界咒语
GENEVlEVE: That boundary spell,
on the other hand,
既然他死了
now that he's died,
我想那就不会再有效了
I imagine it won't be
quite so confining anymore.
你改变主意了吗？
Have you changed your mind?
是的，显然是
Yes. It appears I have.
不要挣托了，卡蜜
-Don't fight it, Cami.
-(SCREAMlNG)
死亡让我们完整
In death, we are whole again.
祝福她，神父
Bless her, Father.
杀了她
Kill her.
享受生命的永恒
Rejoice in life eternal.
你不该承受这些的
You deserved far better than this.
克劳斯，你要知道今天河口的事情
Klaus, you need to know
I had nothing to do
和我毫无关系
with that business
out in the bayou today.
我从不觉得是你干的
KLAUS: I never thought you did.
我打电话是要告诉你神父死了
I'm calling to let you
know the priest is dead.
你的驱逐暂停24小时
Your exile is suspended
for the next 24 hours.
你可以回法语区来埋葬你的朋友
You may return to the
Quarter to bury your friend.
你为什么这么做？
Why are you doing this?
她在黑暗中醒来
She woke in the dark,
不知身在何处
not knowing where she was...
不知道是谁在守护她
...or who was watching over her.
她呼唤的是你的名字
如果你能给她安慰
It was your name she called,
and if you can grant her comfort...
那就这么做吧
...so be it.
听着，我知道我要去哪
OLlVER: Look.
I know where I'm going.
如果你们有人想跟随，请便
If any of you want to follow,
hey, that's up to you.
你们自己决定
-That's up to you!
-(CROWD SHOUTlNG)
基兰死了
Kieran's dead.
你拿到了吗？
Did you get it?
如你所说，就在他的脖子上
It was around his neck,
just like you said.
另外，我对此感觉并不好
PS, I do not feel
awesome about this.
我知道
I know.
但人们会争夺这个
But people are
gonna be coming after this.
卡蜜还没准备好
Cami is not ready for that, not yet.
那现在怎么办？
So what now?
乌云聚集
Storm clouds are gathering.
有人用炸药炸了狼人
我们知道不是我们干的
Someone bombed those wolves,
and we know it wasn't us.
女巫、人类
吸血鬼、狼人
Witches, humans, vampires, wolves.
城市就在暴风边缘
City is at a breaking point.
我们要做好准备
We need to be ready.
先是马赛尔的大屠杀
然后又是河口的炸弹
First Marcel's massacre,
now bombs in the bayou.
我想你准备放弃
这个注定失败的协定了吧
I'll assume you're ready to
give up this doomed treaty.
与狼人的结盟
This alliance with the wolves....
如果要成功
我想你需要这个
If it is to succeed,
I believe you'll want this.
我想我得谢谢海莉让你改变心意
I suppose I have Hayley
to thank for your change of heart.
这城市的裂痕远比我想的还要严重
尼克劳斯
The rifts in this city run far deeper
than I even imagined, Niklaus.
这些部落，这些派系
他们是家人
These tribes, these
factions, they're families,
选择斗争的家人
and families will choose to fight.
我们的家园已一片混乱
Mayhem has descended upon our home,
如果要我选择
and if I'm to choose a side....
敬我们的胜利，弟弟
To our victory, brother.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）